<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Two Hours Late</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/</link><description>The essence of time is experience.</description><atom:link href="http://twohourslate.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 02:19:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Animals and Stars</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/animals-and-stars/</link><dc:creator>bimi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Look up at night! If you live in the city you probably don't see much. We have polluted the night sky with our desire to be constantly in motion, to be constantly entertained and be constantly surrounded by light. I like the dark. I like it really dark and I like to be outside when it's really dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really can't tell if other animals see the milky way and wonder. Isn't that what makes us human in a way? To look up and feel small and yet be so full of wonder and amazement. I say that the Milky Way is in some ways responsible for human progress. At some point our brains were able to appreciate the heavens. Today, we overlook it and many haven't even seen it. Isn't it silly that this opportunity is not valued? To see the stars - I propose that it is one of the important factors that set us apart from other animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>cosmos</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/animals-and-stars/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 01:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>vagrant</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/vagrant/</link><dc:creator>revo</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;Need vagrant and virtualbox-qt. BIOS needs to allow virtualization. Then create folder and vagrant init with link to box file followed by a vagrant up and vagrant ssh. When done vagrant halt.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>linux</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/vagrant/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 23:55:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Installing Ubuntu Mate</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/ubuntu-mate-install/</link><dc:creator>revo</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;First to unxz things.
Then dd the bs from if to of.
Then resize2fs the dev part.
Sounds crazy, I know.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>linux</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/ubuntu-mate-install/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 23:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Something Gives</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/something-gives/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Money &amp;amp; peace. They really are more aligned than one would think. Without money, how would one go about getting all of the things that the human soul has deep in the echo filled well of desire? How would there be diversification of labor? Specialization, and to a large degree progress requires the collective interests that money promotes. Money is second only to language in giving humanity the social tools necessary for cooperation. However, just like too many words doesn't get you much peace so too much money doesn't get you many friends. Now a moment of silence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens when money causes war? Money doesn't cause war. Suffering causes war. Money doesn't alleviate suffering, but giving it does. Words cannot be bought and money cannot buy dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>work</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/something-gives/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 02:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emacs trial</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/emacs-trial/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a trial for an emacs feature for posting.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>emacs</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/emacs-trial/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 08:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Camel Fodder</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/camel-fodder/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;Camels are able to eat just about anything. Have you
ever tried eating a Christmas tree? That's dessert to
a camel. You are what you eat. 'A Christmas Camel
&amp;lt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQwR1Ph36Jo"&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RQwR1Ph36Jo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;gt;'_.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>camels</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/camel-fodder/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 06:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slan go foill</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/slan-go-foill/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;Well, I am using Emacs through a secure shell from Ubuntu to write a blog managed by Nikola on a virtual machine running Arch on a Raspberry Pi. I think I've fallen down the rabbit hole. I know what I hope to find, but I don't think I'm in Kansas anymore. All of this bourne again talk, a python infested environment and a little octocat to keep me connected to the giant web. The world of coders is highly complex and creatively magical. I wonder what the universe is creating with computers. I wonder if the universe listens to the signal of every keystroke on my wireless keyboard. One can only hope it preparing a good and long future. But my more spiritual inclinations are that it may only be good for some and then I realize that good and bad are all just labels for universal matters. A long time is all relative to a light show that emerged from darkness and nothingness. Ugh, now I should see if this works because my brain is sparking.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>thoughts</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/slan-go-foill/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 05:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>