<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Two Hours Late (Posts by bimi)</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://twohourslate.com/authors/bimi.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 17:57:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Creature Comforts</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/creature-comforts/</link><dc:creator>bimi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excerpt from The Prophet by Kahlil Gibran
One hundred and fourty fourth printing, Sept 2007&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Excerpt from on houses: p32-33&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or have you only comfort, and the lust for comfort, that stealthy thing that enters the house a gues, and then becomes a host, and then a master.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ay, and it becomes a tamer, and with hook and scourge makes puppets of your larger desires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though its hands are silken, its heart is of iron.
It lulls you to sleep only to stand by your beed and jeer at the dignity of the flesh.
It makes mock of your sound senses, and lays them in the thistledown like fraile vessels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Verily the lust for comfort murders the passion of the soul, and then walks grinning in the funeral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>comfort</category><category>desire</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/creature-comforts/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 17:49:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Animals and Stars</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/animals-and-stars/</link><dc:creator>bimi</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Look up at night! If you live in the city you probably don't see much. We have polluted the night sky with our desire to be constantly in motion, to be constantly entertained and be constantly surrounded by light. I like the dark. I like it really dark and I like to be outside when it's really dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really can't tell if other animals see the milky way and wonder. Isn't that what makes us human in a way? To look up and feel small and yet be so full of wonder and amazement. I say that the Milky Way is in some ways responsible for human progress. At some point our brains were able to appreciate the heavens. Today, we overlook it and many haven't even seen it. Isn't it silly that this opportunity is not valued? To see the stars - I propose that it is one of the important factors that set us apart from other animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>cosmos</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/animals-and-stars/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 01:35:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>