<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Two Hours Late (Posts by revorefurb)</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/</link><description>Techno data monkey.</description><atom:link href="http://twohourslate.com/authors/revorefurb.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 04:22:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Something Gives</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/something-gives/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Money &amp;amp; peace. They really are more aligned than one would think. Without money, how would one go about getting all of the things that the human soul has deep in the echo filled well of desire? How would there be diversification of labor? Specialization, and to a large degree progress requires the collective interests that money promotes. Money is second only to language in giving humanity the social tools necessary for cooperation. However, just like too many words doesn't get you much peace so too much money doesn't get you many friends. Now a moment of silence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens when money causes war? Money doesn't cause war. Suffering causes war. Money doesn't alleviate suffering, but giving it does. Words cannot be bought and money cannot buy dialogue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>work</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/something-gives/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 02:30:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emacs trial</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/emacs-trial/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a trial for an emacs feature for posting.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>emacs</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/emacs-trial/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 08:47:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Camel Fodder</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/camel-fodder/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camels are able to eat just about anything. Have you
ever tried eating a Christmas tree? That's dessert to
a camel. You are what you eat. A Christmas Camel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="youtube-video"&gt;
&lt;iframe width="425" height="344" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RQwR1Ph35Jo?rel=0&amp;amp;hd=1&amp;amp;wmode=transparent"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><category>camels</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/camel-fodder/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 06:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Slan go foill</title><link>http://twohourslate.com/posts/slan-go-foill/</link><dc:creator>revorefurb</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;Well, I am using Emacs through a secure shell from Ubuntu to write a blog managed by Nikola on a virtual machine running Arch on a Raspberry Pi. I think I've fallen down the rabbit hole. I know what I hope to find, but I don't think I'm in Kansas anymore. All of this bourne again talk, a python infested environment and a little octocat to keep me connected to the giant web. The world of coders is highly complex and creatively magical. I wonder what the universe is creating with computers. I wonder if the universe listens to the signal of every keystroke on my wireless keyboard. One can only hope it preparing a good and long future. But my more spiritual inclinations are that it may only be good for some and then I realize that good and bad are all just labels for universal matters. A long time is all relative to a light show that emerged from darkness and nothingness. Ugh, now I should see if this works because my brain is sparking.&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>thoughts</category><guid>http://twohourslate.com/posts/slan-go-foill/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 05:49:08 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>